[music]
[музыка]
and it’s time
а
to figure it out from the window
разбираться с окна порах
today I’m at the exit from the studio so there at the
я сегодня на выезде из студии так там у
horns enjoy the situation and the ensign so
рожки enjoy обстановка инчей прапор так
today we give up maxim good
сегодня мы поступаемся максим добрый
evening who came big to
вечер кто пришел большой
denounce from america on psychos fer ah yes and
обличать из америки на психи фер ах да а
by candlelight it’s just
при свечах этом просто
not dark there before the ten  where and recession and you
не темноте там до тэнов куда и спад а ты
would be a husband and type on a muffled us with
бы муж и типа на заглушенном us with
lady whalers since colombo is standing like this
lady китобои раз коломбо стоит так
bunker bunker
бункер бункер
so today we park about how
значит сегодня мы паркуемся про то как
Ukrainians take in latvia so I to the
украинцы принимаете в латвии так я к
powerful latvia from after was the outskirts
властным латвии от после была окраина
there which on may close 20 5 kind of weaving
там чего на мая близко 20 5 вид сотки
give the Russian population a trace of
вручить российского населения на следок
radial occupation there, I’ll say, from the hit of
радиальной оккупации там я скажем с хит
Latvia, the rain did rain a bun before Russia, the
латвии дождь таки булочку до россии
wild herd shone this part of the
дикими стадо светил это частка
Russian noses and prowls kumon well, and
российского носами и рыщет кумон ну и
since we succumb to them today from the
поскольку им ся сегодня поддаемся с
bad not and the Latvians for the wild and the
плохого не и латышами за диким и
Russians the rivers in Latvia live so much  I was
россиянам реки в латвии живут так уж я
delivered to the situation in Ukraine so that eggs would
поставляться до ситуации в украине че бы
van and Russia would attack Latvia. I would
яйца ван и нападу россии на латвию я к
help Ukrainians in Latvia, those
украинцам до помогают в латвии те
conflicts between Ukrainians and Russians and
конфликты между украинцами и россиянам и
ow  hell and ios such a ticking
влад и ios такие тикали
moment so
момент так
it's the same reason the master of the step
он же давайте причина мастер шага
[music]
[музыка]
passive to the older person the moving
пассивный к старшей человек the moving
to use is alive so then palvin found both the
to use жив так то палвин застал и
Radetzky union and la stable latvia so
радецкий союз и la стабильную латвию так
this is why we disintegrate the fallen plot
это потому распадаемся падшей сюжет
for example the
например
words of ukraine for the answer
слова украины за ответ
and you eels  smith
а вы угрей смита
russian
русский
look i'm from ukraine and i'm people vlad and
посмотрите я из украины и я людей влад и
ask how they
спрошу как они
rush to vinyl shout how they don't
носятся к винилу крикни как вот их не
think what's going on there to support
мнение что там происходит поддерживать
not potency i think she's [ __ ] and
не потенции я думаю что она [__] и
cutting off and Russian freaks [ __ ] or something
отрезать и русским уроды бля что ли
like that [ __ ] weren't born anymore naha you
такие [__] не родились больше наха
know yes  I understand, but in
разумеешь да понимаю а в
Latvia there are fears that Russia
латвии есть опасения что россия может и
might attack
на латвии напасть
Latvia as people in Latvia think 1, for example, to
люди в латвии как считают 1 то например
protect Latvia or not,
защитить латвии или нет
because we have it too, as we don’t
потому что он у нас тоже как мы еще не
need it yet, well, we kind of want
надо ну мы как бы хотим чтобы нам
America to help us with
америка бы помогла
supplies helps latvian too
поставками помогает latvian тоже
it helps a lot thanks by the way for this but
помогает очень спасибо кстати за это а
the Russian that Vlad see they
вот русский который влад вижу они
support russia and
поддерживают россию и
login parties if they are for the war for putin
партии login если они за войну за путина
on of course there is success but a lot  a lot of
на конечно а есть успех но много много
Russians live flat
русских живет flat и
and shine brightly, but there are now
блеска сильно а есть на приводит сейчас
Ukrainians are coming gold, there is a
украинцы приезжает золотые есть это
conflict between Ukrainians and Russians,
конфликта между украинцами и русскими
in my opinion they are Ukrainians, they will come how to
по моему они украинства приедет они как
say how to explain you where these
сказать как объяснять тебя там где эти
Russian homeland
русское родина
Ukrainians are not there, they go there on the
украинцы там нету они едут там
coast and
берегу и
there are many mushroom brigades
бригад гриб много русской
russian belkin belkin
belkin
daugavpils for a
даугавпилс на
long time
долго
skating the borders russian
русское кататься границы
and you have by the way they are also like we are on fire
а у вас кстати они тоже как у нас горят
there were two languages so that the alatyr russi
же было два языка чтобы алатырский
n was given they
русский был дан
anted to su
хотели
scribe and that we also here they all w
подписаться и что у нас тоже вот они они
nt it was the Russian language load as if th
все хотят было русский язык нагрузку как
y all want not
будто все они хотят не сами уехать в
they want to go to russia themselves, they want russia,
россии они хотят россии
he, too, plays gold systems, that same
я он тоже системы златы играют та самая
situation, they will hate us internally, they will
ситуация нас внутренне они будут
hate ukraine, eat moaning, but they
ненавидеть украину съесть стонать но они
won’t come to russia, books, she came here,
не приедут в россии книж она пришла сюда
and it turns out a lot in the ussr, they also
уж и много вот получается в ссср еще
caught us living like this, the press give, too, I don’t
застали так жили пресса даем тоже я не
10th anniversary since I saw some guy was
10-летию с а я видел какой-то мужик был
in this USSR they didn’t foresee but they want to
в этом ссср не предвидели но они хотят к
bring him back again, we don’t understand hype
его привести снова это не понимаем hype
choose
выбрать
n  for example, Ukrainians who come
например тем украинцы которые приезжают
to la2 now how latvia helps them
в la2 сейчас как латвия помогает им
take their
принимает их
government
правительство
in the arms
на руках
of a
у
neighbor
соседа
small children where only someone goes,
маленькие дети куда идет лишь кого
that is, it turns out if a mother with a child
то есть получается если мама с ребенком
enters to eat until
въезжает есть до
Suzdal because I also loved you with the Poles
суздаля потому что ты я с поляками также
, that is, even without problems more
любил то есть даже без проблем больше
really accepted our
очень приняла наших
okay well thank you very much for your
окей хорошо спасибо вам большое за
opinion glory to ukraine glory to latvia
мнение слава украине слава латвии
hold the tournaments
держите турниры
so teach poland your expression
так научите польши свое выражение
masturbate by throwing dad tight to him in chats and
дрочи скинув папы туго ним в чатах и
it’s worth it for that night and on your thought to
стоит на ту ночь и на вашу думку
fix on that boat and release
закрепить на ту лодку и выпуску
russian aggression options so
российской агрессии варианты так
options are not options  they will give zbroi
варианты не варианты дадут зброи
options issue sanctions so
варианты выдают санкции так
urfa them and
урфу им и
giblets would think at home of cotton wool analysis and
потрошки бы дома анализа ваты думать и
here are real people in oral politics
вот реальных людей на политике оральных
people a little higher than politics know it
люда чуть выше политики знают его не
can’t be dug out for the humidity of concrete let’s say
может вырытых за влажности бетона скажем
it will still come out but at a time it tells them from the
еще выйдет но за раз говорит им из
station to the
становая на
international paradise it’s not so here  Ivan is
международный рая не так тут иван
satisfactory to choose from, but people
удовлетворительный на выбор а вот люди
tell me bachata, I think that
мне говорят бачаты яким думается иной
such words are different  and I think
такими словечками яким думается
doctors who are lost
доктора кто утрачены
write to be assigned a reading clearly to
пишите возлагаться читку ясно чтобы
scare.  just for that, the presenter and
напугать . просто так за это ведущий и
basic censorship so imperiously gave
базовые цензуры так властно вин подавал
my thoughts to wine, I’m not a zopiclone and cutting out there,
свои думки я и не зопиклон и вырезав там
I respect what, let’s say, well, I’ll be dishes and
уж я уважаю что скажем ну я буду блюда и
live emotions, as if alive and expressions
живи эмоции так как бы живы и выражения
and lived long and you will sell them so in your
и долго жил и вы их продану так что в
soul  brutally I think, of course, without
душе брутально были думаю конечно не
thinking, so in the world already put a
подумав так вот так в мире уже поставьте
plus sign, it’s normal like this
плюсик че нормально таким вот такие же
, we’re baking the same past you, these people live like this
мимо тына запекаем вот живем эти люди
, and the minuses are some kind of slave to work with
так а минусы какие то раба работать с
sobs there, both don’t let the whiffer down, both
рыдания там оба не подводи виффер оба
say with a
скажем
sound, pic pic pic
звуком , pic pic pic
put a plus sign  so that respects still
поставьте плюсик чтобы уважает еще
normally around I’m rolling up fer such
нормально около подкатываю фер такие
things
штучки
people will be, but I’m also cursing prices, so
люди будут но цены тоже я матюкаешь так
here people get out of them, we interviewed them, then they
тут люди выйти их мы брали интервью у то
expose their live mother, this
выставляют свои живи мать это
hammer dust was taken by pan andrey under your
молоток пыль приняла пан андрей под вашу
publication from you will be condescending ordeals and
публикацию из будете свысока мытарств а
you came to me right away and  you are there really
ты ко мне пришла сразу а ты там реально
bypassing the girls of the cordon, these dangles
перепуска девчат прикордонной этих
will finish and the guilt is already writing it
мотается закончат и вину уже писать его
after the Facebook broadcast and dad watches new
после эфира фейсбука а папе часы new
videos on the courage windu mandriva and
videos on the courage винду mandriva а я
at first I was just rapping  ortazh so
сначала просто был репортаж так я с
I didn’t say with a signet of wines or Ukrainian,
печаткой вин либо украинскую мы не
and I thought that Belarus
сказал и я 6 подумал что беларусь
if Ukraine doesn’t give me gold
если украина мне ни злата
to trash China is
до трэш китай
doing and when the option will be turbo
делают а когда вариант будет turbo вани
vanis new anti this will be turbo you
новых ведутся анти этой будут turbo вами
are called from turbo vanis so the
так вызывают из turbo vanis так
participants mean it  20 so the
участники на то бишь ляет 20 так что
paid protective one is clear, well, what do you
проплаченный защитную ясно ну чего вы
think for a freebie, that is, butovo
думает еще на халяву то есть бутово
to protect it,
защищать это
too, we didn’t get everyone mixed up with ethics, you
тоже нам не у всех напутал с этики вы
check principles are
принципов чековым
quieter than opposite ours, I filmed it to the
тише чем напротив наших снимал это к
battery of Russian enzymes, I called them so ok, the
батарее россиян enzymes их я им так окей
doctors so sit here  roslyn and high
назвал врачи так тут и сиди рослин и хай
will be uncensored psychosomatics of the good
буде без цензуры психосоматики доброго
excellent swell about yourself and the
отменным отекать о себе да
kids of a person you bachish the audience is not
малышами человека бачишь аудитория не
drunk then people and kivot and fuse
пропито то люди и кивот и сплавляют вы
you as if you live there with such
вот вы словно и там живу там с такими
slavochka we I will be I to the leading stream
славочка мы я то буду я к ведущие стриму
then myself in
то себя в
verbal emotions expression  words dreams and
словесных эмоций выражение слова снах и
mother ok at a time trying to get and who
мать окей за раз пытаемся достать и кого
is the same beads 29 rockin' structure was
это же бусинок 29 rockin' структуре
born already for keiko rocky in
народився уже за кейко рокки в писля
pisla to get it for the importance of latvia tartu
добыть оное за важности латвии тарту
twin with the union  well, but this is his
twin при союзе же так а вот такого его
position, and after all, the knife and those who did not give up the
позиция и ведь нож и не отдавших
Russian about my friends and holes russian
российском о моих друзей и дыры russian
these live in latvia,
эти живут в латвии
let's go for latvia in the evening,
давай за латвии а
but I'm from ukraine, I'm asking people and sweet
вот я из украины я людей и сладкие
how do you see the conflict in
спрашиваю как вот вы видите конфликт в
ukraine how do you feel about  him ukraine
украине как вы относитесь к ним украине
what is your opinion a
какое ваше мнение
member of this
член этого
terribly feel about this so
ужасно отношусь к этому так
terribly feel about what is happening
ужасно отношусь к тому что происходит
in general
вообще
nationality russian or latvian
национальности русский или латыш
as if i don’t sort it out how i live
как бы не сортирую как бы я живу в
in latvia
латвию у нас очень много русских и они
or will it hold Ukraine back from how the technical opinion is,
или подержит украину от как техни мнение
this is how this situation happened, we
вот как произошла вот эта ситуация у нас
got such a hack a little bit, how to say
пришел такой хак немножко как бы сказать
such a small drop re-entered such a drop
такое небольшое перезашел такой перепад
and everyone started
и начали все
for Ukraine,
кто за украину
who is there for Russia,
кто там за россию
but I think it’s wrong it’s
но я считаю это неправильно
wrong to argue green or for
неправильно что спориться green или за
Russia  yes, yes, I think you live,
россии да да я считаешь ты живешь
let’s say our state is ours, but in
допустим нашем государстве наш но в
latvia, let’s say if you live, you
латвии допустим если ты живешь ты всю
lived there all your life next to me since childhood
жизнь там жил рядом у меня с детства
let's say he joined the fight here as a
драку допустим он примкнул салтук тут
friend for Russia, the game is why all of a sudden, but
дружеском за россию игра с чего вдруг но
they say there that they will all be
они же там говорят что у них все будете
in the guys and tell you it
в ребята и говорить тебе это кажется
seems to you that the train is please to the
вот тебе поезд пожалуйста
conflict and we are starting, I
конфликту и мы начинаем я
also noticed not the same toys
тоже заметила не вот так же игрушки
that are in Ukraine  they didn’t ask,
которые в украине они не просили хотят
they want to attract Russia to themselves like
они хотят россию притянуть к себе вот
this, that is, they, passing to Russia, I also
так то есть они проходя до россии я тоже
noticed this, but for example, now there are many
это заметил а например сейчас много
Ukrainians Ukrainians in Latvia
украинцев украинцев латвии
honestly obviously don’t meet me, I
честно явно не встречаю мне очень много
work a lot, but I read how much I
работать происходит но я сколько читаю
listen and how much I know
сколько слушаю и сколько я знаю знакомых
friends  a lot of us came more
у нас очень много приехало больше
dictate
диктуют
12001 for latte it’s a huge
12001 для латте это огромная
huge numbers for our small
огромные цифры для нашей маленькие
latvia it’s huge and for example there are
латвии это огромный а например есть
such things as conflicts between
такие вещи как конфликты украинцев
ukrainians to ukrainians who came with russians
украинцам которые приехали с русскими
who live
которые там живут
there happened peter
случались питер
I’ll tell you honestly not because they are
скажу так честно говоря не потому что в
mostly women with a child  and
основном это женщины с ребенком и их
no one should touch them, it goes without
никто трогать не бой на это само собой
saying that in Latvia we have such a
понятно что латвии у нас есть такой
principle that no one would  will touch not
принцип что никто не будет трогать не
women not with a child, someone will
женщин не с ребенком месте кто-нибудь
dare, well, of course, he
посмеет ну само собой понятно он ее за
will answer her for it
это ответит
everything will happen later when it
все произойдет потом когда это
ends, but this is basically when it
закончится но это в основном когда это
ends, let's say,
закончиться вот допустим вот наконец то
finally, these idiots will start to go home and
вот эти придурки начнут уходить домой и
finish will shoot and  all this
заканчивать будет стрелять и все это
will end all this is over, I don’t even
закончится все это закончилось я даже не
know how to put it correctly, they
знаю как правильно выразиться
will take away their rotten equipment, the
заберут короче свою гнилую эту технику
old one that they have, they
старую которую она у них есть они
think that they are banal, well, in
считают что они банально рода ну на
fact, it’s not, but they will take away and
самом деле это не так но они заберут и
all their rotten equipment will
всю свою гнилую технику оттуда уберутся
get out of there, get out of  Ukraine and let people
уберутся с украины и дадут людям
live in peace, normally, and in any
спокойно жить нормально же и в любом
case
случае
they will have to rebuild it, but in Latvia
им придется это отстраивать но в латвии
it will be so
это будет так что
[music]
[музыка]
if the Ukrainians come, but the husbands of these wives
если придут украинцы но мужья этих жен
who have now run away, you will
которые сейчас вот сбежали нанесешь
come to Latvia, they fled as children and
приехали в латвии они сбежали детьми и
now the husbands are about to  the war will end
сейчас мужья вот-вот война закончится
until we rebuild the country yes, well, there is
пока страну не отстроим заново да ну
nowhere to live, they will come to live a little,
негде жить они приедут немножко пожить
let's say Vlad and they are from here and what
допустим влад и они при отсюда и что
will happen to the  yami, they will be afraid
будет с ружьями они же будут бояться на
because if this person saw what
потому что если это человек видел что
happened here, he won’t just
было тут он так не будет просто
register,
регировать а
and you have Vlad here and a very large Russian
у вас тут влад и очень большая русская
Russian community, so it turns out that the Latvian is left
русская община так получается осталось
to the
до
edge, but I support, I am friends with
края латыш но я поддерживаю я дружу со
everyone
всеми
, yes, there is, you just understand  there are
есть да есть просто понимаешь есть
Russians there are technically Russian, that is, they don’t
русские есть тически русски то есть не
create parties there for
какие-то там партии создают они там за
friendship with Russia, they want
дружбу с россией они хотят
because they would decide to transfer Russia here,
потому что перевести россию бы сюда
they want kittens, of course, yes,
решили тину хотят котят конечно да
they constantly pulled prices, and that’s all, and
тянуть они постоянно тянули цены и все и
they all suddenly broke off with
оборвалась они все у
me such one  was who terribly
меня вдруг такой один был который ужасно
believed in Putin, still believes, he
верил в путина до сих пор верит он до
still has a nose, but he communicates and I tell him,
сих пор носа но общается и я ему говорю
I say no need to communicate myself, I
я говорю не надо сам на общаться я не
won’t trunk, I don’t want to become just so that
буду ствола не хочу стать просто чтобы
not from this, not just a
не из этого не не просто не возник
conflict,
конфликт
but sir, she says  no, I want to chat with you
но сир она говорит нет я хочу с тобой
games no, I say we don’t need
общаться игры нет я говорю не надо нам
to chat, but there’s no point, but the chicks are
общаться но нет смысла а птенцы в том
pulling this pipe, this one, how can I say
тянет вот эту трубку вот эту как скажу
how you said this thread
как вы сказали вот эту ниточку и
in Latvia and right there in Latvia t  again and
в латвии и тут же в латвии тоже и опять
again in this blister as it was before
туда же в этот как было раньше блистер
everyone is in this [ __ ] all this we will all be
все в это [__] всём этом все будем
homeless why why he most
бомжевать почему почему он же скорее
likely lived watercress with he saw it like that and
всего он жил кресс с он видел это так и
you understand and now they live better
понимаешь а сейчас живут лучше
I don’t know
я не знаю
no I can’t
нет я не могу
I don’t  I’m small, I have only
я не у меня маленький у меня всего лишь
29 freedoms, my husband understood me, I’m 49 years old in the USSR
29 свобод понял мой муж мне 49 лет ссср
and found my father to eat here there
и застал есть здесь
will be times when it might
батька будет были времена когда может
be a little bit good, but in Europe
быть было хорошо чуть-чуть но в европе
it’s better, but in Europe it was better, but here he gave the
лучше но в европе лучше было а здесь дал
mountains here, do what you want, go  where
горы здесь делай что ты хочешь иди куда
do you want to do,
ты хочешь делать
well, let's say, you
ну скажем так
say
высказываешься
how you want to go, don't touch it,
как хочешь идти никто об этом не трогай
and there, God forbid, even if you utter a peep, everyone is
а там не дай бог хоть пикнешь все
tied up prison
завязали тюрьма
or execution,
или расстрел
look in latvia people have no fear
смотрите в латвии нет у людей опасения
that putin can
что путин может так же как на полу грин
attack the history of latvia and lithuania just like on the green floor  we
и напасть на истории латвии литву у
have latvia to honestly say everything is cool and
нас латвия честно сказать все клево и
honestly say it is very cool
честно сказать она очень клевая
well, I think it is
ну я так считаю это
recorded
записано
very afraid of us Latvians are so shy of the
очень боятся нас латыши такие пугливые
ball and at the joints I am Latvians but no I said
мяч и стыках я латыши а нет я сказал я
right away I told my Russian friends to
сразу сказо я своим друзьям русским
everyone with  it hurts
сказала всем стоило
if you go to us, I all have a machine gun of my
если вы нас пойдет я все у меня автомат
hand, I went to meet and those who are
руки я пошел навстречу и те которые у
my friends, God forbid, you stumble
меня друзья не дай бог ты оступишься
you through the same gate,
тебя в те же ворота
well, let's be real, everyone has their own country,
ну будем реальными у каждому своя страна
for example, it turns out, as it were, into two three
например получается как бы на два три
members, that is,  Latvians’
члена то то то есть у латышей
confidence natasha needs to be protected it
уверенность наташа надо защитить
turns out
получается
why where will it come from
почему откуда она возьмется
now let’s say
сейчас допустим
[music]
[музыка]
how to say it’s hard to say some think
как сказать тяжело сказать одни считают
yes I think it’s honest that no because
да я считаю честная что нет потому что
how can you calculate well because
как ты можешь посчитать ну потому что
if you never know we have Russia here we have a
если мало ли у нас россия вот у нас
border with Russia
граница с россией
it’s not her  Vanya is fighting with us, Putin is fighting,
не она с нами воюют ваню воюет путин
but look, if we also thought
но как смотри будь вот у нас тоже думали
Putin Putin, I communicate a lot with
путину путину я общаюсь очень много
Russians and they support the war, of
русскими и они поддерживают войну
course, it’s not only Putin, a lot of
конечно это не только путин очень много
people
людей в
watched everyone support ia regnum st
смотрела все поддерживают иа regnum ст
Yes, they say that’s because you are that
да они говорят вот потому что вы та
because  that you yourself are rivers because you are
потому что вы сами реки потому что вы
above and now pile on Malta, this is not
над и вот навалить на мальту это не
only one, we will be a service;
только один будем сервис все вот с
they are nasty against or
противными против или
they are normal guys and
брать они нормальные ребята а русский
write out the Russian
выписать как вроде
as if they turned on the shot in the head and all of them, as it were, will
включили в голове shot и все они как бы
pile up there as a memory.
на память навалится там у нас ей у нас
I’m being led
это пересматриваю я не виню я не ведусь
to all nationalities that, let’s say that
на все национальности которые скажем что
we are being conducted on the Internet, yes, it’s all the
у нас ведется по интернету да это все
Internet, there is physics somewhere,
интернет к бывает физики где-то
propaganda, detail, well, different,
пропаганда деталь ну разное
well, in fact, I know a lot of people
ну по сути дела я очень много знаю людей
and I have family friends from Ukraine, they
и с украины есть у меня знакомые семьи
tell you to [ __ ] bomb again just [ __ ]
тебе говорят [__] опять бомбят [__]
they are bombing me and on the other side the
просто бомбят и у меня другой стороны
Russian is the same friend he says
россиянин тот же друг он говорит
or they still say it’s not rsi bombing
или они еще говорят это не rsi бомбит
it’s there Ukrainian nationalists
это там украинские националисты
[music] the
[музыка]
plane
самолет
is there yes here they are, as it were, everything that is
вот есть да вот они как бы все что им
uncomfortable in their head they think it is not
неудобно в голове они считают его нет
it or not they are so  they make a video or
его или нет они так делают видео или
deny it and say that it’s the other way around, like
отрицает и говорят что это наоборот типа
it’s easier for them how to make it easier for them to
им проще как сделать им проще что
make it easier
сделать ее проще
to swear or they didn’t even know whether it would be
поклясться или не даже не знали
confirmed to their state like them
подтвердится своему государству типа им
it’s easier why think for yourself if
проще зачем самому думать если
you come up with the state for me, but at the same time
государство за меня придумай но при этом
they don’t understand that it
сами не понимают что это
will end badly,
плохо кончится
that means he can sit in some kind of
тем значит он может сидеть в каком-то
downtrodden and power there without water without the light of
забитом и силе там без воды без светом
history with why yes and yelling at us
истории с для чего да и орать на нас
Ukrainians but he won’t utter a word  the
украинцев но слова не пикнет своему там
president is good for his governor there,
губернатору президент хорошо
although at the same time there are connections in [ __ ], but
хотя о при этом связи в говне а вот
look at the piece of paper you have in latvia there
смотрите бумажку у вас в латвии есть
are some organizations there now that
какие то там сейчас организации которые
ukrainians are there to block
там украины чтоб блокируют
transportation in russia they
перевозки в россии
release
выпускают
in poland there is everything from poland belarus they don’t
в польше есть все из польши беларусь не
let trucks in
пускают грузовики
so i don’t hear much
так я не слышу особо
hangar for the state there is no period,
ангар за государство не периода нет у
neither my father
меня ни у меня батя дальнобойщиков
works for truckers,
работает
but no matter how, because the finishers are not a
но как бы нет потому что доработчики не
nationalist,
националист
they
они всем
don’t need everyone, but the truck, for example, carries some
не надо но фура например везет какие-то
medicines in Russia from products in
медикаменты в россии от продукты в
Russia, that is, boyish muscles and the
россии то есть пацан ционный мышц а
state doesn’t go up  no legs because there
государство ни вверх ни ног потому что
are no such orders and such a sea does not happen,
нет таких заказов и не происходит такое
in fact, the only thing we have
море собственно у нас единственное что
is to put on, go, import is assigned to Russia,
да это одеть иди назначен в россию
which they  need doesn’t happen,
импорт который им нужен не происходит
but how to squeeze it, leave it without resources,
но как как зажать оставить без ресурсов
it’s kind of cruel, but they will
это как бы жестоко но они поступлю они
act, they act, they fight, and if they are left with
поступают они воюют а если их оставят с
resources, they will develop and
ресурсами так они будут развиваться и
bomb even more all this is
бомбить еще больше всем этом есть в этом
good, everything is good, thanks for the conversation, it
хорошо все спасибо за разговор очень
’s very nice that latvia lips  support
приятно что латвия губы поддерживает
ukraine and don’t support odessa joy
украину и не поддерживают одесса радость
also all spa ukraine glory
также все спа украине слава латвии
latvia be such a teak character so we didn’t
вот будь такие тиковый персонаж так мы
know they want to
на знал хотят бачу в
chat acacia there Ukrainians they are ukrainian
чат acacia там украинцев они украинская
already you appear I’ve been on the right for three hours of code
уже вы появляюсь я уже три часа кода
in that I’m talking about Russian war
справа в том что я российском о война
wide 20  bachat me straight
говорю широких 20 бачатой меня прямого
Russian mugs for she so could I
российскую кружки по она так мог бы я
straighten up so we have pan chipane for
выпрямляюсь так у нас пан чипаней for
teens in the chat belarusian spoiled in
teens в чате белорусскую попортится в
belarus why are you just
белоруссии че вы просто
ukraine ole bull butts the higher she is
украине оле булл приклады чем выше она
on let these scrolls frame ala need
на пусть эти свитки рамочка ала нужно
us here the international coalition
нас тут международного же коалиция
is planned
намечается
we are bachyls  502 Latyshev way, like rivers, in
мы бачылы 502 лад латышев как реки в
principle, is unambiguously
принципе однозначно
disgusting, and in Ukraine, unambiguously the uterus and
противен и в украине однозначно матку и
let the anti-Russian position, etc.  how long ago the
пусть антироссийскую позицию и так давно
profession and
профессии и
in the evening in the hall and
под вечер в зале и
at a time we succumb to the Russians and the same
за раз мы поддаёмся россиян и те же
will be in
будет в
Vlad itself and so you will also be all sorts of
самом влад и так ты тоже будут всякого
daddy pigs and you just have to drag it like that and over
папа свин и просто надо тащить так а над
them russia find they live in latvia and why
их россия найти живут в латвии и почему
don’t you go like this  up to 6 kW and the dialogue
ты их не идут так вот до 6 квт и диалог
turned out, put a plus sign and by the age of the
получился поставьте плюсик и к возрасту
check and you that they will pile on for
чеку и ты что они будут наваливать за
Russia, and the minuses will still be just the
россию а минусы все-таки будет просто
fault of
вины
such a show, I think
такая показы считаю
Andrey
андрей
that he writes from home to the
что вписывает из дома на
Buyan from and she drove me light from the
буяна от и она меня наехала свет от
Ukrainians I’ll say Andrey Khmara Kozhevin
украинцев скажу андрей хмара кожевин
strata, yes, I’m already trying so there is
страте да я уже я стараюсь так имеется
once again a nailit, since losing
лишний раз найлит так как проигрывать
ran to something of the clan was
бегал к чему-то клана
printed by Andrey, the surgeon Minsk will answer
печаталась андреем хирург минск ответит
for everything so plus sign, you really think that in the
за все так плюсик правда думаете что на
wild and always carry they will pile on for
воле и всегда ношу будут наваливать за
wine and bury it if they weren’t instructed, they wouldn’t
вина и зарыть это не наставлены не бы
be and  disgusting and alla from the child we know
был и противен и аллы от детского знаем
and the groove and about the Russian corner you and so the
и паз и про российскому угла ты и так
potency of the steam of the
потенция steam
Russians and in latvia kind of mirror russian
россиян и в латвии вид зеркалить russian
in ukraine let's go up to me
в украине давайте поднимемся ко мне
vouchsafed to the daiquiri of the motherland there
сподобилась на там дайкири отчизны
good evening good  th evening and at the edge of glory
добрый вечер добрый вечер а у краю славы
and gold yes yes yes
и золотые да да да
beautiful I looked from ukraine I people from
красава смотрели я из украины я людей из
latvia ask how you feel about the
латвии спрашивают как вы относитесь к
war in ukraine in
войне в украине
your ukraine
своем украине
you will have an anode for russia for ukraine
вас будет анод есть за россии за украину
how
как у
we have people from ukraine some people
нас есть люди с украины какие-то
come there we help them all
приезжают кто-то там мы им всем помогаем
with how we can and what city are you from what city
с как можем а вы с какого города
to speak from what city angry vape
чего говорить с города какого angry vape
but you yourself are russian or latvian
а вот вы сами русский или латыш по
nationality I am Russian Russian but
национальности я русский русский а вот
well, as if they were Russians, they depended on
ну как бы русские они зависели за
Ukraine in this conflict, well, in
украину в этом конфликте ну на самом
fact, Turkey was all so divided very
деле турцию все так разделилась очень
much, like someone, but then here, but
сильно типа кто-то зато то тут зато
now everything is very divided,
теперь все очень сильно разделилась не
not there, Russian from Russia, there is a montage of
то там русский из россии там монтаж
amazement like  By the way, there is such a thing that
изумление типа кстати вот есть такое что
here is Russian, yes more for Russia, everything is
вот русский да больше за россию все так
like Ukraine, Latvians, even Ukraine, they have such a thing
украину латыши даже украины есть такое
because of this conflict between
они при из-за этого конфликта между
Latvians, Russians, by the
латышами русскими
way, there were some small ones
ну кстати бывали какие-то маленькие там
there  and at rallies, there were some kind of riots there,
на митингах что-то бывало какие-то там
but there were very few of them, but
бунты но типа очень мало какой а вот
now a lot of Ukrainians have come to
сейчас очень много украинцев приехало в
Latvia, so if conflicts
латвии так если инфильтратом конфликты
between Ukrainians and Russians are infiltrated, by the
между украинцами и русскими
way, yes, some Ukrainians here
ну кстати да некоторые украинцы здесь
are starting to download rights very strongly, such as,
начинают права качать очень сильно типа
for example, they sat down in
например их засели
short, well  in short,
короче ну вот короче
well, so the
ну так что
Ukrainians,
украинцы
well, they say, or at least something we
ну типа говорит или хоть что-то это
call knives a peasant, don’t let out the
называем ножи мужиком не выпускаете
country, the
страны
state pays them, yes, it turns out, well
государство платит им да получается ну
, something like that, and the hotel there is also
типа того так и отель там тоже место
a lot of good places, and in Latvia there is no
очень много хороших а в латвии нет
such settlement through me, for example,
такого поселения через я например
attacking Latvia  also in the way of Lithuania and
нападет на латвии также на лад и литвы и
Estonia,
эстонии
I don’t even know about this how the
вот насчет этого даже не знаю как вас
tank treats you in the way America
относятся танк на так америке стране
helps the country, I didn’t go deep because here are
помогает я не углублялся потому что вот
Russian toys in Russian, they are all
русский игрушки в российскими они все
against America, everything is disgusting, it seems like a
против америки все противно то вроде как
big one will attack them, we also don’t know
большой нападут на них мы тоже не знаем
here  this situation
вот эту ситуацию
that you can
что ты можешь
look at, for example, here
осмотрите вот например вот
you speak Russian at home,
вы дома говорите по-русски
Latvian, how
латвийский как у
we actually have more Russians
нас у нас на самом деле больше русских
why the party-goer himself is not inside there according to the
чему тусовщик сам не внутри там по
census, you are 25 percent Russian
переписи ты на 25 процентов русских
according to the census 20 percent Russian
по переписи 20 процентов русских
for some reason, the
зачем-то
Russian site knows a lot, it’s
русский сайт много знает это на самом
actually a lot of those who
деле очень много тех кто этот этот язык
didn’t live this language during the Soviet Union,
при советском союзе не жили получили она
for example, here’s your university education
например вот обучение у вас университета
in  new schools only on me,
в школах новых лишь на меня-то у
we have all the main bumps they are forcing us
нас главные все шишки они нам заставляют
now they are trying to ban the Russian language in general in all schools
сейчас пытаются вообще во всех школах
type with this there are
запретить русский язык типу с этим
big problems with
большие проблемы с
what the problem is the
чем проблема
problem is that well, in Latvia in general,
проблема в том что ну латвии вообще
you just don’t like Russian very much,
русски просто не любите по очень сильно
Vlad
влад вирус
perceives the virus very much in Russia  as an occupier on the
воспринимает россии как оккупанта на
Soviet, take it off even before the whole
советский снимай это еще даже до всей ты
war, in general, all this is not yet the
вот вообще войны всего этого еще не
occupiers of Ukraine now, but in
оккупантами сейчас украины а сороковых
the forties we didn’t make
годах штука на копировали ласты у нас не
up the Soviet Union,
было составили советского союза
for example, in your opinion, what would be bad if
например по вашему что плохо будет если
there was a Latvian report of guilt in Latvia.  in
в латвии будет латышские доклад вину . в
Russia, Russian has strengthened bran, and the
россии русский укрепил бранский а всем
problem for all
проблема учиться на латышском языке
children to learn in Latvian is that some parents
детям в том что какие-то там родители
were born in Russia to raise their
родились в россии воспитать своего
child in Russian, and it’s not very
ребенка по русский язык типа и не очень
convenient for him to learn this Latvian
удобно ему будут учить этот латышский
language, it’s very difficult, I want to
язык это же вот очень сильно сложно хочу
watch too  it turns out if they
смотреть тоже получается если они
were born in russia it’s like that but it’s difficult for them to
родились в россии так но им сложно учить
teach if they can leave for russia
вот если они смогут уехать в россии
why didn’t they leave for russia but
почему не уезжали в россии на но
it’s not known why it’s
неизвестно почему типа кому то здесь
just more convenient for someone to stay here because relatives are
просто удобнее остаться потому что родня
here or some kind of inheritance, too,
тут или какое-то наследство тоже
inheritance can be sold, it just
наследство можно продать просто
turns out russians  people
получается русские перину там люди
come to france on a featherbed there and now
приезжают во францию и сейчас
french britain are learning english
французских британию учат английский
latvia ukraine they don’t want to learn the
латвии украины они не хотят учить
local language which turns out to be
местный язык который получается
wrong eat this yes
неправильно есть такое да а
but look for example you have
вот смотри например у вас есть
people who drown there join
люди которые топятся там присоединится к
russia there
россии там
[music] have a
[музыка]
good evening and a
хорошего вечера и
phone on your face
телефон на лицо упал
Did these fall like it, come on, what did I
эти ли понравится по давай что я тут
write correctly in the chat aku
правильно написали в чат аку
contrast if you find it  I’m less and less
контраст если отыщется все меньше
Aleppo metals and how to become the main thing
алеппо металлы и как стать тем основном
these bumps want us to learn to ban
эти шишки нам хотят обучения запретить
there in Russian, this is who on the topic of the
там на русском языке это вот кто на тему
moment so vichuh that the face of such people here is
моменте так вичух что лицо таких тут
the rhetoric itself that we have a plus sign in Ukraine,
сама риторику что у нас в украине
so I’ll
вот я вот коломенского
build up Kolomna because now I would start  it all
нарастить ибо ныне бы начал это все
squeaked like in Europe and then it
пискнул вроде и в европе а потом и
turned on and you are trying to trace the needle,
включилась и следа иглы пытаешь а чего
why can’t you get it right
чего ты не можете получить его правильно
get it and someone can see it here I want them
получить и кто-то ему тут видно хочу их
from ft sibel tyumen so there are friends of the
от ft sibel тюмень так туда дружкова
world so because there is a fight and
мира так потому что там драка а
Europe is
европа
smooth  bayonets tse europe there as far as
гладко штыки це европа там по мере ведь
apathetic oysters he doesn’t want you there
апатично устриц он не хочешь же ты там
but not in your own way stf would be Russian
но не своему порядком stf бы российскими
so long-standing microfibers with common
так давними микроволокна with common
flash the author writes that the nod chocolate
flash автор пишет чего кивок шоколад
hit on ideals it will sometimes
попала на идеалах можно будет иногда
be
было
Ukrainians before these experiences
украинцев до этих опыта сидят 4
you have 4 boys sitting in your car  there is no right to vote to
пацанчика машины у вас нет права голоса
hide the custom for us and the girls how
укрыться обычай нам и девчат как
it was so Ukrainian dudes devops
это же было так украинский чуваки devops
then after the collapse of the union our Ukrainians
то после развала союза нашим украинцам
would be given Baltic passports to
выдавала балтийский паспорта бы
Russia  kim and ukrainian ukrainians
российскими и украинскими украинцы
have chosen a russian one to get a doctor in
выбрали российский до получаются врача в
latvia such a category yak not hulks from
латвии такая категория як не громадян из
karachi for heating they call it live
карачи на нагрев называют в нем живут
all-in dances in jamaica political
танцы олл-ины на ямайке политических
rights here she can vote in elections
прав тут она может голосовать на выборах
and can be removed we are here c30 them then
и на может быть убраны мы тут c30 их то
she was born
она родилась
writing pisa radiance bill and writing
писля pisa приходу радианс купюру и писи
forties hands on the territory of latvia
сороковых руки на территории латвии
1000 so whose ancestors acquired and in latvia the
1000 так чьи предки нажил и в латвии
gifts of the gallic to bathe her so
дары галльской купать ее так
began this cheese ears dc miracle here is a
началась этот сыр ушки dc чудо вот
clown please they say well there at [ __ ]
клоуна пожалуйста мол ну там у ебашьте
cl and russians and the sound of vitaly on not to take
кл и россиян и звук виталий на не взять
italian from  also since I’m not there before
италийской из также раз я не там до
spain, spanish chat without any problems, so
испании испанская без проблем чат так
it’s nice clearly so that we
что приятного четко чтобы мы прям
give direct ringtones to displace, oppress them, not the
рингтоны дают вытеснять притесняют их не
Russian lightning shkolota, but in the cic of
российском молнию школота а вот в цик
ukraine and the cis, it’s apolitical there
украины и снг так то тут аполитична там
, the Kremlin is specially blown away by moscow
специально уже сдувается кремле москвою
and these people then get out of you  shoot
и эти люди потом выкручиваются вы пулите
strong bodies like ours everyones you about an
сильных тела как наши всякие ты об
extra lot then petr im leaving so
излишней партии потом петр им уйти так
on so
далее так
kind and nokia 3310 on
добры и nokia 3310 на
a nokia machine
машине nokia
so don't mi  kro shafts love hears from any
так не микро валы любишь слышит из любые
is silent and correctly saved therefore it was
молчит и правильно спас поэтому
cleaned why so but I will say it
почистилось почему так но я скажу так
lasts now I could plow and lie, but to the
то сейчас бы мог пахать и лгут а к
forms there is supposedly a gram of unity and that the
формам же якобы там грамм единство и что
daughter is improving to coward the film for 30 rock
дочь улучшаются трусить фильм за 30 rock
me well, I like often for 30
me ну я типа частую за 30 тропе у нас
people give us cyprus on the path and come vinci
дайте люди кипр и и приезжайте винчи
ukraine and spend your hands already there with the world an
украину и затратить руки уже там с миром
agency according to the formula I would like to
агенство по формуле так-то то хотела бы
think I chopped it
думаю изрубила
up I’ll go up
поднимусь еще
another Latvian
одно латыша я кисть цветку у него было
it’s like this and here we’ll
размыт ну начитка у него так а тут мы
say on the prices for the competition it was beautiful this
скажем на цен на конкурс красивым этом
was the effect of the
был эффектом
filling of the order so but this and kid
начинка ордена так а вот такого и киду
kevin denunciations so this is a
kevin доносов так это
tick moment until
тиковые момент до
good evening I went out without ukraine I
вечер доброго вышел без украины
didn’t understand so there were borders they were looking for oh cool
не понял так был границ искали ах круто
I’m from ukraine and people acid from firmware
я из украины и людей кислоты из прошивок
slope from poverty in ukraine is
от бедности склоне в украине
very, very how to say
очень-очень как сказать
who you don’t wave very negatively
кого не машешь очень негативно
drying has
сушки
come now of
пришли сейчас всех
all lines of the dash and all that
всех линий черточки и все такое
and people who are Russians in latvia they
а люди которые вот русские в латвии они
support growing  these are
поддерживают россии
clearly in this, too, and there is
явно в этом тоже самом деле и есть
trouble,
беда
because when I did, but in our city there was a
потому что когда я вы но у нас в городе
rally against the war, and wait until the
бяла митинг против войны да и жди до
Latvians came out, and
вышли латыши да и
ethnic Ukrainians, I didn’t see a
этнические украинцы я не видел там очень
lot of Russian-speaking people there, yes, they are
много русскоязычных да они
under the influence of TV, if
под влияния телевизора все если
not, I  I didn’t see them,
нет я не видел их того
but it worries me too, but although they
но это меня тоже беспокоит но хотя они
behave very, very quietly with us, they don’t
ведут себя у нас очень-очень тихо не
talk about the war, not even these, even the
говорят про войну не не этими даже
St.
ленточки георгиевские которые держит
such a
такая
box is an
коробка
automatic
автоматическая
famous zf box and this box has a
знаменитая zf коробка а у этого коробки
logo letter z
логотип буква з у
my friend always erased this letter yes
меня знакомый вечно стирал это буква да
it is
это
not connected with the war they do
войной не связан
n’t want anything to do with this month of
не хотят ничего общего с этим месяце
russia with this fault
россии с этой виной
yes we have everyone has already closed the
да у нас да у нас уже все закрыли
borders completely the assassin’s stopper was
границы полностью стопор ассасина
blocked  from Russia, yes, all the reasons, even the
перекрыли с россии да все повода даже
traffic flow and everything back and forth is
автомобильный поток и все туда сюда
no longer in it oil im borg [ __ ]
больше не в него нефть им борга niggas
in the bar of the year and
in bar года и
for example there were some you had
например были там какие-то у вас было
three of the toys did that  m cars will have to
три из игрушки делали там авто придется
Russia or from whom there isn’t such a thing didn’t happen
россию или от кого нету такого не было
before I
раньше
didn’t notice something for Russia that
не заметил что-то за россию что там у
we don’t have much experience there, they don’t remember Russia
нас особо нет опыта не россии вспоминают
only when May 9,
только тогда когда 9 мая да
yes, then he goes, although we also have these
да тогда ходит он хотя у нас тоже эти ну
pains and pains to and  these ribbons are all
с и боли к и эти ленточки все под
banned and they can’t walk around the city like that
запретом и так ходить по городу они не
, but if someone hung this ribbon in the car,
могут но если в машине кто-то повесил
when its
эту ленточку когда его внутреннее
interior you can do what you want,
пространство вам делать том что хочет но
but now get out of Ukraine for a long time,
так выходи сейчас мы надолго из украины
people
людей приехала
came from the sea, as far as I know, a
женщин от морской насколько я знаю
little more  400 children only yes, and
чуть больше 400 детей только да и
how many women with children up to the
сколько женщин с детьми до
figure I won’t say, but well, I haven’t met 6, I
цифру не скажу но ну я 6 не встречался
can even communicate at our rate in the
общался умеет даже у нас ставке в
Moscow theater with a dart meeting with
московском театре дартом встреча с
Ukrainians so that they can talk to them how to say
украинскими чтобы их у как сказать
garden socialize communicated
общались сада социализировать общались
yes-yes-yes-yes-yes  so that they feel
да-да-да-да-да чтобы у них они чувствуют
that they are accepted by the way we all
что их принимают да кстати у нас все
refugees live none in gyms I
беженцы живет никаких в спортзалах мне
don’t all of them have a room and a hotel
не них у всех есть номер и гостиничный
TV shower but the restroom about paying
телевизор душевой но уборная об оплате
it they pay or the state pays them
это они платят или государство им платят
for it  we have a state party before
за это у нас государство party до
our self-government, and
самоуправление наши и
even now on the news I heard somewhere
даже сейчас по новостям слышал где-то
already issued at 11000 before
уже выдано в 11000 до
returning to work to Ukrainian
возвращения на работу до украинским
citizens,
гражданам
so those who are almost all who,
так что те которые почти все которые при
while that is, yes, they can work and
при то есть же да они могут работать и
they
они
yes, yes, although they have  now the full provision of
да да хотя у них шас полное обеспечение
their food provides them with medicine,
их едой обеспечивает медициной
in my opinion today, yes, already the good news is
по моему сегодня да уже радостная весть
Ukrainian in the intersection was born the
украинский в с пересечением родился
first one already has a pregnant woman
первый уже есть беременная женщина
left and it will turn out
уехала и получится
cool
классно
ventspils instance cool but
вентспилс instance прикольно но
even there the local newspaper says that
даже там местной газете написано что у
this child will be provided with everything to
этого ребёнка будет все обеспечена
manipulate this kind of itself the mayor
манипулировать саму данный вид мэр
came  with this he gave a gift was
пришел с это дал подарок
photographed yes but in my opinion no but
сфотографировался да но по моему нет а
what else are they waiting and waiting for one with
что ради еще ждут и ждут один с
batteries but yes this is good
батарейками но это да это приятная
news but
новость виде но
I can tell as soon as the
могу я могу сказать как только началась
war started before but we all have flagpoles yes
война до но у нас всех где флагштоки да
everywhere in the city near ours  the flag is
везде в городе до рядом нашим флагом
sure to hang exactly like
обязательно висит вот такой точно как у
you have behind your back and
тебя за спиной и
not a day was filmed all the time to fly the
ни дня не снималась все время лететь
baltic countries estonia  latvia and lithuania and
страны балтии эстония латвия и литва и
ukraine are not looking for were friendly and the
украина не ищут были дружны и
modern ussr we were when we were or the ussr
современный ссср мы когда были или ссср
we supported you you were in decline or also
мы вас поддерживали вы на спаде или тоже
then there was
тогда плода
a lot of fruit I remember my father was they
очень много я помню у меня отец был они
went to lithuania there something printed
в литву ездили там что-то печатали
newspapers and carried somehow  it was impossible to
газеты и везли как-то сюда нельзя было
print here and it was already handed out here to this is
напечатать и тут уже раздавали к это
also
тоже
good thanks it would be very interesting to
хорошо спасибо очень интересно было бы
say all the words of latvia glory to ukraine
говорить все слова латвии слава украине
glory to ukraine until
слава украине до
[music]
[музыка]
a todos compartment you quickly moment we don’t
a todos отсека вы быстро момент мы не
wonder if people are straightened
задумываемся ли людям расправлены просто
just their dish left and well these  countries and an
у их это блюдо уехал и ну этих странах и
anthem was and now he died on a zinka she left the
гимна был и вот погиб на зинка уехала
same way she loved in latvia so
так же она любила в латвии так вот
let's say
скажем
we can mark the same earlier so
мы можем на помечаем таки раньше так
let's say I see these businesses so you
скажем вижу эти бизнесе так и вы
send it right to seem 3 hours to you
присылаете правильно казаться 3 часа вы
car and these are the stories and comments of the one
машине а вот такие истории и комментах
who said let's say 50  -anniversary immediately
сказавшего скажем на 50-летие сразу
appear there comes at an age
появишься там приходит на возрасту
takes a picture that we are there I once try to be
фоткается что мы там я раз пробуем
involved thought but he doesn’t know how we
причастным думали но не знает как у нас
love these politicians somehow the
люблю эти политики как-то вот ест их
people of the river eat them hmm because why so their boats
люда реки хм ибо чего так их то лодки
here you are, he is looking for a clearly
вот вы он ищет к однозначно
pro-Ukrainian anti-Russian position and
проукраинская антироссийской позиции и
from in the mixer they know tac toy themselves there are
от в миксере знаются tac toy себе там
young seniors here,
молодые тут старший
let's say the presenters say
такие скажем ведущие говорится
intelligently says everyone from a
интеллигентно говорит у всех от
simpleton's integrity is clearly anti-Russian
простаковой целости четко антироссийская
and clearly pro-Ukrainian, and
позиция так и четко проукраинская причем
Biden put the Ukrainian ensign from you
байдена поставила украинский прапор от
tell us from here at Nastya ensign  and
рассказываешь отсюда у насти прапор и
Ukrainian 12 to interfere with it, after all, it means
украинский 12 мешать в она ведь значает
all Peter pays them, and so I think it
всю петр им платы и так то я думаю еще
’s still looking for a social thick native
вот ищет социальный толсто нативный
mark up so that Ukraine Russia about
размечаем чтоб украина россия про
Ukraine will step on the model
украину так то наступит на модель были
, and there would be a teak uncle for
бы и вон и так выше тиковый дядька на
memory, so Belarusian, that is, they ask
память так белорусских то есть просят
so I remember for some moment we
так меня памятаю за кого-то момента нам
were hounded for measles to become and change the
ей заборонили кори статься и менять на
carcass for a red green carcass to cut off the Kyrgyz women
червона зеленых тушку отстричь киргизки
to the doctor St. George's shavings dehydration
до врача георгиевская стружка осушка
outbreak in Belarus a district police officer for
вспышка в беларуси участкового за
defense to us
обороны нам
so
так
I'm to you Ukraine yellow-
я к вам украине жовто-блакитный у нас
Blakitny we have a green tiron
тирона зеленая
so well, let's have  us now we are
так ну и давайте у нас сейчас мы сегодня
rich today today we have 7 storylines
богата сегодня у нас 7 сюжетики перебрав
going over either because I will  speaks less and
то ли потому я буду меньше говорит и
shows more, I think I’ll
больше показывать я думаю мне выше
be able to listen to them on the air more than they can
сможет их доступных послушать их бы
, but for months people and let’s listen today let’s
эфирах так а месяцев люда и давайте
listen to two young people so
послушаем двух молодых так
such butane headlights
такие бутане фар
if you don’t want to
если не хочешь
often
часто
ukraine
украина
now
сейчас
also spoke to
тоже говорил
another guy he also we also talked
другим парнем он тоже мы тоже поговорили
about this situation
про этой ситуации
I entrust revenge to you, too, the question we
вручаю месть тебя тоже вопрос у
have inside I know that disinformation of
нас внутри знаю что дезинформация
information is everywhere and the
информации это везде и
moon 6 percent is such a youtube one
луна 6 проц это же такой youtube один
channel where
канал где
where it says that your president, like, allegedly
где говорит что ваш президент типа якобы
he was not in Ukraine, he was like
он не был в украине он был типа
and
и
he left Ukraine, but more this is
он покинул украину но уже больше это
some  then
какой-то
there are all the tents,
там все палатки
which is their project,
который вот это них проект
this is information
это информация
that
что
he is not in Ukraine now,
он сейчас не украины
I understand that, well,
я понимаю что ну
who needs it, but this is my place, that
кому это нужно но это мое место что
it is
это
because I
потому что я
[music]
[музыка]
watched how he is, what kind of situation is
смотрел как он какая ситуация
so
такая
normal,
нормальная
I can’t say because I
не могу сказать потому что я
don’t have anyone  did not ask
никого не спрашивал у
us if the Ukrainian flag is everywhere everywhere
нас вывод ли везде украинский флаг везде
on the tram on the buses on the stomach the
на трамвай на автобусах на живот
Ukrainian flag I see more than we
украинский флаг вижу больше чем мы
actually if the server
фактически если сервер
but this  about the fact I
но это факт я
don’t mind in Ukraine in general, it’s just that I’m for
не против в украины вообще просто я за
peace, the war is why watch how
мир война это зачем смотреть как
people die
люди
fear that,
опасение что
well,
ну
it’s possible because why not
это возможно потому что почему не
why not if you can’t have this
почему нет если не может у вас этому
second story, what kind of history is not
второму история какая нам история не
worse than you, in my opinion,
хуже вас по моему не
everything is needed  maybe
ну все нужно возможно а
if you think about it further about,
если еще там подумать дальше про
for example,
например
why NATO,
почему нато
how I sing, I also understand Russia,
ну как я пою я тоже понимаю и россию
because well, like this type of NATO is
потому что ну типа им этого типа нато
already closer closer closer to Russia
уже ближе ближе ближе в россию
why
почему
you
ты
constantly
постоянно
need no one
надо ни на кого не
I don’t understand why this is not possible  probably
я не понимаю почему не можно это наверно
because how do you when you
потому что как тебя когда у тебя есть
already have a layer like that
уже пласт такая
you
тебя
are 4 maximum
на 4 максимум
further there it’s so easy about democracy the
далее там же так просто про демократию
shield talked with hanging out
щит поговорил с тусуется
authoritatively today’s half can be seen son
властно сегодняшние тайма видно сын там
there in russia to ukraine and so on
в россии до украины и так далее вот
will be the soonest to show you
спинка будет скорейших показать вам
allowing me to drag me was turned on
позволяющие на тащу меня было включается
and manually juveniles and
и вручную молодь и
facebook or broadcast back I would decide
фейсбук или трансляция назад я бы решил
that let's say bart and appear like that
что скажем барт и показаться так
put a plus sign then uva  you press such things into the coulters
поставьте плюсик то уважаешь в сошники
even and 6 the map shows and they
такие штуки чет и 6 карта показывает и
fight on equis there are sound defects
на сражаются на equis там дефекты звука
and minutes the
так и минут
defect is all on the path with slopes fer
дефект это всё на тропу скатами фер
you know that there is he runs rocks so writes
знаете что есть он бежит скалы так пишет
varnish you yourself pro-Russian quien
лак не дошла ты сама пророссийская quien
es wedge of the Baltic states to there already there  even the
es клин прибалтики до там уж там дуже
black ice eggman of the Russian population
black ice эггман российского населения
to a long price and the locrian itself label
до длинных цене и сама локриан ярлыку
you
you
panas about it so for disintegrating one more
панаса о нем так за распадаемся еще одно
lads here we are massacre of the social
хлопцы вот мы резни социального
layer cif
слоя сиф
get out natasha I chose peaks
выбираться наташа я выбрал я пиках
throwing out here sew with God forbid that we
выкинув тут пришить с дай боже чтобы мы
all said so Russian shares Latvian
все так говорил российской акций латыш
busha  you twist when life live mix it seems
буша крутишь when life live mix казаться
6 Russian so we ascended your code was
6 российскую итак мы взошли был ваш код
so help with the subject laundered and the post was
так помощи с предметным отмыл и посту
enough and
хватать и
here you are what kind of massacre you got there worst
вот вас какие там резни попалась worst
removal vanya so here is Saladin a circus
выноса ваня так вот саладин цирковой
character in order to ragnit and
персонаж для того чтобы рагнит и
slender roses 300 who fell from the massacre
субтильный роз 300 кто пал от резни
worst  since you fell and here's another
worst вами поскольку валось и вот еще
people ask you how do you feel
люди спрашивают вы относитесь
[music]
[музыка]
support
поддерживать
you yourself turns into latvian russian
вы сами получается в латвийский русский
or latvian
или латыш
[music]
[музыка]
we communicate more in Russian
больше по-русски общаемся
and
а
there are no such sheepskin coats in latvia there are a lot of russian
нет такого дубленок в латвии очень много
people
русских людей
this is a river of debts
это реке долгам стоит
and it turns out but how, for example, local
и получается а как вот например местные
russians treat but there or is it
русские относятся но там или есть это
meningitis support for russia it
менингита поддержку россии это
[music]
[музыка]
in general like for you
вообще типа за вас
charred
обугленными
ukrainians are ready to come the
украинцы готовы приехал
president and
президент а
there is no conflict between the Ukrainians and the
нету конфликта между украинцами и
Russians who are there now,
русскими которые там сейчас
well, I haven’t met
ну да не встречал
honestly,
честно сказать
not
не
because
потому что
[music]
[музыка]
our Ukrainians like at home and loading you
наши украинцы типа домах и загрузки вами
because like the Russians say well
потому что типа русские говорят ну
[music]
[музыка]
why do you speak Russian well, damn it, well, to
зачем по-русски говорите ну блин ну чтоб
understand each other, we
понимать друг друга
’ll talk
пообщаемся
he somehow
ему в чём-то
turns out to be
получается
Russian-speaking Ukrainians who came
русскоязычных украинцев приехавших
more than for Latvians,
больше чем для чем латыши то
well, there, but
ну там а
in this he gave a daw how many Russians,
в этом дал галку сколько русских
for example, the percentage
например процент
[music]
[музыка]
53 percent
53 процентов
turns out latvia is our brother,
получается латвия наш брат у
here the Russians say, but we
нас вот русские говорят а вот мы напали
attacked Ukraine green and did not join  in NATO
на украину грин и не вступила в нато у
minutes she died there is latvia and estonia
минут она погибла есть латвия и эстония
in kind that japan is attacking not
в натуре что вот япония нападает не
only that local legs are disgusting
только что местные ножки это противно то
[music]
[музыка]
I know that there,
знаю что там
well,
ну
like I’m
типа мне
peaceful, these negotiations are shorter and
мирные вот эти переговоры короче и
you need to sign a contract, and many that you wo
надо подписать контракт а многие что вы
n’t go like
не пойдете типа
[music]
[музыка]
well, I don’t think the war will go further,
ну как бы я думаю тип не дальше война
for example, like a mouse, who has the best
ты например как мышь у кого лучший
situation now who is stronger now  in
ситуация сейчас кто сильнее сейчас в
ukraine or russia in this
украине или россии в этой
regard, in terms of that
в плане что
this damage to
этот ущерб
ukraine tor is normal, well, at home,
украине tor нормально ну там дома вот
it’s all destroyed,
это все порушено
but you trust the leg of the Ukrainian support to protect your leg,
но а по защите ногу украинским опоры
ukraine wo
доверяешь украина победит
n’t
не
be
стану
impossible, but
невозможно а
there is a vlad method and fears that rubber
есть влад методи опасения что резина
will come to latvia and
придет на латвии а
why
почему
[music]
[музыка]
there are also a lot of
тоже очень много
us
нас
[music]
[музыка]
you can’t guess for a long time either,
давно это тоже не угадаешь
so these are the things we would have in our Russian
так вот такие дела бы у нас российским
workshop, we’re evil of yours, so Svetlana told me about
цеха нам зла твий так мне сказал о себе
herself and not that Putin would have attacked the
светлана и не что там путин бы напал на
way he sees what Russians are here for what
лад вид ему что тут русские для чего на
they were attacked and concerts of letters of Russian
них напал и концерты грамоты российских
Russian lightning cilia ferrets there
российском молния реснички хорьки там
Mariupol will give the same rich people domineeringly
мариуполь дадут же богата людой властно
Russian lightning and Friday Russians
российском молний и пятничных россиян
such prices from
такие цены с поняла
we understood little and thoughts of carved vrs on the shroud
мы мало и думки резных vrs на саваня
peregl  when I saw the videos and all the same I
переглянувшись ролики и все таки я
babbled that I gave cracks and give
бахался че давала трещин и давать еще
one more video of this and so but I think for happy
один ролик сема и так но я думаю за рады
so comedies are the most such promo whists
так комедии это самый такие промо висты
and dialogue
и диалог
in the barrier and the possible and the barrier well
в барьером и возможным и барьером ну
let's try
давай попытаемся
I kept and cream with 1 peg
я держал и крем с 1 peg
whom you  on a year from his appearance poured
кого you on годом от его вида подлил
sing about working in fact then under and
sing about working in fact потом под и
couldn’t his khufu form latvia
не смог его хуфу форме
riga riga riga aim from
латвия рига рига рига айм фром
khmelnitsky and
хмельницкий а
loved lagreat the
любил lagreat
clock
часы
was anton the language at brick and clap
был антон языке при brick and clap
taught him on had to about english and
научит его на пришлось об английской и
so starting
так начиная
achieved laughing though he  I myself,
достигнуто смеяться хотя он сам сама
at least a dude, I understand that, too, those who walked will
хоть чувак я так разумею тоже ходивших
talk to a Ukrainian, then 7 it
поговорит с украинцем то 7 это так
happened
получилось и
and you gave him a horseshoe to give me
ему вы подкова выдала мне
funny to receive, I think that it is
смешно получать я думаю что и на нем
possible from both in the media, but it’s okay
можно из оба по сми а так ничего
in
в
English, then read that and generally
английском его то почитай что и вообще
without problems  above stamped the streets sharks
без проблем выше штампом улочкам акулы
english
владение английским языком
and poker open
и poker open
[laughter]
[смех]
if so then bingley only we are at home for
если так то бингли лишь мы дома на
someone generally scary type
кого-то вообще страшно типа так
as it is correctly
как правильно
said there will be a date of death sign so young
сказано будут дата смерти знак так молод
in  well, get on the English highway,
влад ведись на трассе английского
they say, don’t get rid of the core frequency somewhere,
говорят не избавитесь куда-то сам ядра
it’s Moldovan, there was
частоту это молдаван вот была на таких
some kind of international marriage and
каких-то брак и
young Moldovans, and you’re not quieter older
молодь молдаван и вы не вот тише старше
so that the Russian vil says, and the noise of the
чтоб российской вильно говорит а и шума
camp is still not every English, I’m
лагеря таки не каждого английского я
Russian people by us  yours so I think
российскую людьми нами ваш так я думаю
it would be cool and we had a refusal the
что было бы клёво и у нас был отказ
situation that we have little shared
ситуация что у нас мало делает shared
english and so not the
английскую и так не
russian family of aura in rushed so and
российская семья ауры в ломанулись так и
broken english so we will change
ломаную английской так так мы изменим
clear it is afraid so rewind
очисти боится так rewind
very beautiful
very beautiful
this one was so angry and
этой был так и злилась
noted two  these human skoda
отметился два этих человеческому skoda
yeti
yeti
we yesterday so english we immediately have
мы вчера так английской у нас на сразу
melodics in 4 pin chief 4 english and
мелодики в 4 pin шеф 4 английском и
mind wipe it so normal that i stuffed
разуме вытрите так нормально что я набил
russian write or for russian before pan
русская пишу или за российскую до pan
for teens visited russian we mean
for teens посетил русском мы разумеем
only
только
ukrainians don’t like candles we usually we speak
украинцы свечи не любим мы обычно мы на
english  I mean, so we can that,
английскую разумею так что можем той
maybe, an English landing, so Russia,
может и английской посадка так россии
Belarus, to the pasha, I can see that I gave bran, it’s
беларусь к паши видно я дал бран это
great, I love Russia, which is
прекрасно люблю был руси что
listening  I
прослушивается своей малым и вас
honestly wanted to miss the
разумеем так честно хотела пропустить
spring Shafirov as a kid and you understand, I myself was in Latvia,
весеннего шафирова сама была в латвии
plus I couldn’t use
плюс рода читами не смогла сандр во-о-он
cheats  on the
ступор от rubbage ну и перешли на
socio-political there you are so at a time
социально-политическую там ты так за раз
on the conspiracy of you can hello hello
на заговор из ты сможешь привет привет
bye evangelical until May 5 us 21a
пока евангельских до 5 мая нами 21а
subject to talk on the back is political
предметом поговорить на спину политична
there and since with him you can’t
там и так как вот с ним и не можешь так
touch him like that iksha who forces what you and
ему трогаться икша кто силы что вы и
keystone exclusion clubs  such here they are
keystone исключения клубы такие вот они
about there and the
про там и
youth series there, you further
молодежный там сериалы ты дальше
round off for us for young people there,
округлить у нас для молоди там
but to find the right topics there
а вот найти с такие темы там правильную
about politics, so you can torment where
про политику так мучить можно там куда
you need to choose from the movie the sky level the
надо избрать из фильма the sky level the
isle of cheats an English hole and your friend
isle of читы английская дыру а друг ваш
is a health center  these temples at risk pocket
так здравпункт эти храмы на риск карман
risk and learn and file in english usa
риска и узнаем и файла на английской сша
on this power
на этом власть
so math and I can laugh and sit down
так math и смогу посмеяться и садится
cool ras time when it's wrong two days two
круто рэса раз когда не так два дня два
bits of cl and po  look, there is no sabotage of the massacre
бита кл и посмотри саботаже резни бывает
and you growl and you laugh of your own accord and let
нет и рычишь а ты сам собой посмеяться
such calculations wake up now kim
дае такие расчетам проснёшься сейчас ким
and the horseman it’s cool I’m in a situation and
и всадник прикольно я ситуацию и
hummocks of the best so I want to appoint
торощин лучших так хочется назначив об
to talk about it teasing them pleases and in
этом говорить подкалывает их радует и
short this rick ray I think that we
короче этом рик ray я думаю что мы
are crumbs today and
сегодня трошки и
listened to his bag  the cycle of people is so much more
слушал его сумке цик людей так больше
friend dear ok to be inserted in our latvia
друг милый ок вставляться у нас в латвии
h peter capacitive side whose petr
ч петр емкостного боку чей петром
hadeyuc see how to insert up to russia and
hадeюcь видите як вставляться до руси и
how russian and latvia are left to
як оставляются russian и в латвии до
blame in ukraine and to russia and imperiously
вины в украине и до россии и властно
rose dmitrovka by 100 and so
поднялась дмитровке на 100 и так
an elderly volume but completely  such cash register
пожилого тома но совсем такая касс
hangs out distributed dykes live in
тусуется распространили дайки живут в
ukraine and I respect that
украине так и я уважаю что
people there work out some and
отрабатывать люди там неких и
istanbul there their ticket to Muscovites
стамбульских там их ticket москалям
atomic scientists with ours then so we will tell
атомщики с нашими тогда так мы расскажем
we are at fault and what we want
мы по вине и что мы хочем у
we can also come true in the retinue we
нас умеет еще и сбывается в свите нам в
have
нас
no fault in us  in front of his horns and padme, our
нет вины перед его рога и падме то наших
allies have lumps of pockets with German, having
союзники глыбы карманы с германом
tried it
опробовав вот
with prefixes, the Caucasus, someone
с приставками кавказу пробовал у кого-то
has so many there are not on our uniforms  ata
есть так много нет на нашей форматы
data si wants girls on the beams it’s so
данных си хочет дивчины по балок это так
there in the morning before pi matrix the girl will follow
там утром до пи matrix дивчина последует
so that they are attacked by you with her
чтобы на их раскручивала напали ты с ней
grinding would sound I tried
размола бы зазвучать я пробовала твои
your eruption often to create a bearded
твои извержение часто создать бородатые
hairy man and why not so much less
мохнатый мужик и почему не так уж меньше
beard then put it out right away  so
борода то так и сразу выставить это так
I’m long on teak chimes like, well, are
я длинных на тиковых перезвоны как ну
you new
новые ты
for the republics of the Caucasus, perhaps with a bead and
за республик кавказа разве бусиной и
parsley of power, so it turns out olap, we
петрушки власти так получается olap
analyze it, so here and I tried there,
разбираем так тут и я пробовал там идут
you come from Estonia from carved prominent faces, okay,
вы из эстонии из резных видных лиц окей
just puts 0 to 10 today the bay to you
просто ставит 0 до 10 сегодня бухте к вы
issuing so 0 take a look  to the water I’ll sit down
выпуск так 0 загляните к вода сяду
liquid and and that I don’t stick you between
жидкого и и что вас там не сую между
zero and give you, but through there I didn’t get slapped in the face, you
нулем и дать а через там на пощёчин не
can Dusenov’s way from under the
сподобилась можно душенов путь из под
region now is like a tire with
областью сейчас подобно шины с
details of the release, so don’t forget to
подробностями выпуску так не забывайте
vote, we have experience of him
проголосуете у нас есть опыт его него
detective nata
сыщику нату
latvia release of Russian aggression
латвию выпуску российской агрессии на
they won’t let you think so, they’d issue
ваши думку так не дадут зброя бы выдают
sanctions so 45 votes
санкции так 45 голосов
then the 53rd brigade
там ты бложике потом 53 бригадой
was given to the spoon to celebrate, I’ll say that
подавалась на справляя скажу что
they are there to run after the brush there that it will
их там бегать за кистью там что будет
be millions there you can
это миллионы там можно там там
fool around there they show and languish
дурачитесь там показывают и томитесь
return you need to again wriggle out of the
верните нужно опять там покривляться из
dust inward slightly from there the horse
пыли внутрь слегка из там коня
unicorns ali well, let’s say I adore,
единорогах али ну скажем я обожаю еще
let’s say
скажем
I don’t  I want to turn it off often I want
я не хочу выключать часто такие я хочу
beauty I will apply a large audience
красе буду прилагать большую аудиторию
so all i nastia brush here are the right thoughts,
так all i nastia кисть вот правильные
who are they wearing and yes they didn’t
думки то кто носят и вот да не
irritate the content
раздражали контент харин буду так такому
line to
тысяч полярников так линейки мыслить
think less so and in nature I
заходи меньше так и на природе этому я
said one had 1 year on
какой сказала одна оказала 1 году на
ice on metal here Potanin and that’s
льде на металл тут потанин и в тому и
Cavill and to my aunt here and hearing and so
кавилл и к тете сюда и слуха и так то а
I’m a queen and then you will be holy to me so
я queen и потом будут меня ты свят так
that is to say with people  let's say here it
то бишь с людой аки скажем вот он
is that it just appears there
является то что там просто появляется он
and listen, it
и слухай
is removed, annoyed the content and the
снимается раздражали контент и не чинно
appearance of it does not change decorously, it can’t be in the ear,
меняется вид ним она в колос не можете
so then we are our inner stormtrooper  I have a
так то мы мы штурмовику свою внутреннюю
political position, so after all, wearing up to,
политическую позицию так ведь ношение до
say, our state to the path in our
скажем нашей державы до пути в нашей
state, so let's say through c, paint
державе так и скажем через c покрасим
our sweet like a firefly and lived so
наш sweet так светляком и жила так что
beautiful fairy reasonably for 2 ours herself was
красиво фея разумно за 2 наш сама
honored with the subway beautiful English
сподобилась метро красивые английских
these are days with lucky positive release you
это days with lucky позитивный выпуск вы
give heads happen  well, yes, we’ll hang in the dark, what
даёте башки бывают ну да на хмара висим
will be the brush started in such issues
че будуте кисть начатые в такие выпуски
took place, I jump already to drink for
состоялись я прыжке уже пить за добавьте
add one more boat and so I think that’s just
еще одну лодку и так я думаю вот как раз
at work
за работой
less and the formats of the troshka so the combines are
меньше и форматы трошки так комбинаты
just a la jolla pulling out the dave and the
просто a la jolla вытащив дав и ноуте
wild laptop they were going to combine  from it’s so
диким они были будут комбинат из так
simple, with a signet, I could have counted the
просто я с печаткой бы могли бы счет
cell so then
клетки так потом
oh, I was honored to give
о сподобилась дайте
us, but I won’t be the director of these, I’d roll
нам а режиссера этими не буду раскатал
out the look of things at work now and I’m
бы сейчас взгляд вещи на работе и я
chopping here I want to go right away and exactly
рублю вот едущий хочу сразу бы и ровно
like that we can note ii it’s cool it turns out
так можем note ii прикольно получается
that’s how people do adab  likes and at the
то так народ сделать адаб лайкает и по
command of the subscriber who is the first time
команде подписочки кто первый раз
leather than at 10 pm coming in tone
кожаного чем на 10 вечера приходом в тон
and maybe 10 pm can be left so
и может 10 вечера может быть запасе так
so most assume that you are six on
так самых допустить что вам шесть на
you can squander it,
искал можете промотать это кто-то
let's do it together like this if you are a
давайте дружно вот так если ты че
funny Russian accent, the homeland of Russia
смешной российский акцент родине россии
will be a car 4 these doors will not answer, in
будут машина 4 не ответят эти двери в
principle, you can where to get them to the
принципе можно можно куда их чтобы
rubbish audience, so these girls on the
добиться трушке аудитория так вот эти на
stream are then rich in stock, and on the
стриме девица потом в запасе богата а на
stream we are  the same for the audience so and therefore I will
стриме мы же на аудитория так и а потому
formulate you let us 6 through there
сформулирую ты пусти нас 6 через там
no trace must find someone who
никаких след должны найти кого-то кто то
wants to and so to the earthly I thought
хочет а чтобы и к земного я вот думал
you can
можно вы
work
работаете
mini prizes for her coolest
мини призы за ней прикольнейший
common.py 2 before such a shorter early we don’t
common.py 2 до такого короче рано мы не
left before it was so I think that
покинули до того было так я думаю что
now he came up with neck stitches while
сейчас он шейки стежки по придумали пока
you downloaded an hour in the east so put
вы скачали часу на востоке так ставим
likes deprive us of the room for more yes
лайки лишаем комнаты нас на больше да
who wants from there not quite a primitive
кто хочет от туда не совсем примитив
path of the church 6 to play a whole flood
тропы церкви 6 разыгрывать целый потоп
they are Svetlana
они светлана
cars how to pay off debts 5
автомашин чем ли погасить долги 5 куплю
i will buy in ukraine for excavations in ukraine for 1 1
в украине за раскопки в украине за 1 1
out of 100 water for 15 l n no there teak
из 100 воды на 15 л н нет там тика
flocks are sold at 9 power hansa about donetsk
стайками продаются по 9 power hansa про
us tag audio to islamic both
донецк нам тег audio к исламской оба
quieter coming soon t  everything is so about the bed
тише скоро свои приходы то постели все
, because it also means you are for yourself in the
так потому значит еще вы для себя утром
morning, it’s so
у это так
real that you have a husband and if he were a nadka, you would find this and
бы он был надька вы бы нашли этому и в
that was and how cool the YouTube thing is, well,
тому был и как круто штука ютубу так ну
or the Internet that
или интернету что
you can choose to tear off a ticket vip
можно выбрать отдирала ticket vip
convenient, but I’m people on in on the mountain, nike started
удобный а вот я люди на в на горе почала
in the fall, the cotton wool product is so all you
nike осенью продук вата так все ты
switch your wow, well, to the wah show, that
переключаю свою вау ну на шоу ваха так
’s what our currency is called, and with which we
зовется вот и наша валюта и коим мы
pay
расплачиваемся
in fact like this 2020 2323 we have so
фактически так 2020 2323 у нас так
vladimir domain so Moscow itself 10 bucks
владимир домен так сама москве 10 баксов
everything to  this repair the water limit on
все чтобы этот ремонт лимит воды на
stretching would be rich today the video was
протянула бы сегодня богата был ролике
already dioxin for
уже диоксин за
chat so today we have a little sleeve of scarlet
чатак так то сегодня мы мало втулку алых
chat so and talking videos there I would have
чате так а беседует ролики там уж я бы
decided to let us at least more videos to enter
решил нам хоть и больше ролики входить
share these live and the breaks of the
поделитесь этими живым и разломы
larger one is so small and the disk is tual
большего такому малом и диску туал это
ok everyone all the tobacco industry tomorrow
окей все всем табачной индустрии завтра
from 20 20 and who is called in stock do not
от 20 20 а кто называется в запасе не
forget to leave comments on
забывайте оставлять комментарии на
jumping on the cheeks from the hem
прыгать по щекам с подола всякий
so that you are still an audience like this is
от вы все еще аудитории подобно это так
what Omsk was rented from, from
то чего омску добывалось напрокат что с
their very Russians there to smooth
их самых там россиян до с гладкой
toxins in the cinema and was honored just as
токсинов по кино и сподобилась так же
normal, let’s say there were
нормально было еще скажем там был и
matyuki ranks cartoons kind of icy tactics to
матюки чины мультики вид ледяные тактики
tear incisura this is further in short to everyone
рвать incisura это дальше короче всем
evening garna and glory to ukraine
гарна вечера и слава украине
[music]
[музыка]